{
    "subject": "resource/Karl_Weierstrass",
    "predicate": "ontology/doctoralStudent",
    "object": "resource/Carl_David_Tolm\u00e9_Runge",
    "human_readable": "Karl Weierstrass was a doctoral student of Carl David Tolm\u00e9 Runge.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9831575751304626,
            "question": "Was Carl David Tolm\u00e9 Runge a teacher of Karl Weierstrass?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9505753517150879,
            "question": "Name the professor who supervised Karl Weierstrass's doctoral studies."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9263922572135925,
            "question": "What academic connection existed between Karl Weierstrass and Carl David Tolm\u00e9 Runge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9180393218994141,
            "question": "What is Carl David Tolm\u00e9 Runge known for in relation to Karl Weierstrass?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8788765668869019,
            "question": "Who was Karl Weierstrass's doctoral advisor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8752859234809875,
            "question": "In what capacity did Carl David Tolm\u00e9 Runge guide Karl Weierstrass?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8717132210731506,
            "question": "Who supervised Karl Weierstrass's doctoral program?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8505902886390686,
            "question": "What was the relationship between Carl David Tolm\u00e9 Runge and Karl Weierstrass?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8201366662979126,
            "question": "To whom did Karl Weierstrass study under?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7125489711761475,
            "question": "Who served as a mentor to Karl Weierstrass?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Karl Weierstrass was a doctoral student of Carl David Tolm\u00e9 Runge.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7691_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To whom did Karl Weierstrass study under?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7691_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the relationship between Carl David Tolm\u00e9 Runge and Karl Weierstrass?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7691_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who supervised Karl Weierstrass's doctoral program?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7691_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7691_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7691_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7691_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7691_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7691_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7691_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7691_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7691_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7691_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7691_50.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThis triple is incorrect because according to the documents, it was actually Carl David Tolm\u00e9 Runge who had Karl Weierstrass as his advisor, not the other way around."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not support the claim that Karl Weierstrass was a doctoral student of Carl David Tolm\u00e9 Runge. In fact, the information provided indicates that Karl Weierstrass was Runge's doctoral advisor."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Carl David Tolm\u00e9 Runge was Karl Weierstrass's doctoral advisor, not the other way around.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "It states that Weierstrass was a student of Runge, but the provided text says Weierstrass was Runge's advisor. Advisors are those who guide students, not the other way around.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information states that \"Although Weierstrass was his advisor, he had not suggested the topic of Runge's thesis; rather this had come out of discussions he had with other students in the Mathematischer Verein in which he was actively engaged.\" This implies that Karl Weierstrass was an advisor to Carl David Tolm\u00e9 Runge, but it does not indicate a reversal of their student-teacher relationship.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Carl David Tolm\u00e9 Runge was a doctoral student of Karl Weierstrass, not the other way around.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}